Let's go prep a ninja creamy. We're
making a cookie butter or biscoff ninja
creamy. So, I always start by weighing
out the dry ingredients. The best way to
do this is to get a cup on the scale,
tear it to zero, and start with the
ingredient with the most volume, which
in this case is going to be sweetener.
So, we're doing 40 to 45 g. Obviously,
this seems like a lot, and it is a lot,
but remember, we're making ice cream.
Ice cream uses
60 to 100 grams of sugar per pint. And
if we want to recreate that, we need to
use a similar amount, but obviously a
caloriefree version. So that's 45.1.
This is the Zantham gum. Sometimes I use
a 1/4 teaspoon to measure this, but
usually I just measure it um on the
scale. So we're going to get this to
45.9ish.
Perfect. So that's8 gram which is uh 1/4
teaspoon if you do that math. And then
we have some salt. Same thing here.
We're going to do about 0.5 to 1 g.
That's about 1 g. Perfect. And then also
for this cookie butter flavor, we're
adding some cinnamon in. So we're doing
3 g. So we're going to get this to about
50. That's a little under 3 g. Looks
perfect. Now these are all our dry
ingredients. We're just going to swirl
them up. This is so the zantham gum gets
dispersed and it's easier to mix into
your milk. So now we'll grab our actual
pint. We'll tear the scale and then
we'll add our milk. As you guys know, I
always use this Fair Life fat-free milk.
400 g
402. Perfect. Okay. Now, the vanilla
bean paste. I usually just eyeball. You
can also use vanilla extract. We're
doing one teaspoon, which is about 5 g.
Okay. Um, that was an absolute [__] ton.
I usually do like half of that, but
apparently that's only 5 g. We're not
stressing. That's fine. Now, we got the
cookie butter extract from Lauran. We're
doing about a teaspoon of this as well,
but we're going to measure this. Um,
boom. That's about 4 and 1/2 grams. That
should be good. Now, we're done
measuring everything. We can put our
scale away. Get this down. And then
we'll go dry into wet. And then we're
just going to mix it up. Immersion
blender. Still highly recommend these if
you guys don't have one. They work way
better than a milk frother or a hand
mixer that I used to use and I know a
lot of you guys use.
The key with this is to keep it super
low in the pint. If you bring it up in
the pint, it's going to overflow. So
don't say I didn't warn you. So just do
this for at least 30 seconds to get it
fully incorporated. And then you can
just throw your cover on.
Bring it over to the freezer.
Set her in.